<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>London-Edinburgh-London on ultra-cycling.de</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/categories/london-edinburgh-london/</link><description>Recent content in London-Edinburgh-London on ultra-cycling.de</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><copyright>© Michael Lihs 2022</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ultra-cycling.de/categories/london-edinburgh-london/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>London-Edinburg-London 2022</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-08-16-lel-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-08-16-lel-2022/</guid><description>London-Edinburhg-London (or short &amp;ldquo;LEL&amp;rdquo;) is probably the second most famous brevet in Europe (after Paris-Brest-Paris). It is organised by Audax UK and takes place every 4 years. With a 1 year delay, due to the Corona pandemic, I had the great pleasure to join the 2022 edition of this iconic bike challenge. Here&amp;rsquo;s my story.
Getting there By car and ferry
After careful consideration, we decided to approach London by car.</description></item><item><title>London-Edinburg-London - results</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-08-16-lel-result-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-08-16-lel-result-list/</guid><description>Since there is no &amp;ldquo;official&amp;rdquo; list of finishers (yet) on the LEL website, I wrote a little script to generate a rider list from all riders that started the race&amp;hellip; it shows all riders with their start and end CPs and their riding time.
Result list for London-Edingburgh-London 2022 riders
You can find the online version here
If you want to contribute, the source code is available on GitHub</description></item><item><title>London-Edinburg-London - my packing list</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-07-29-lel-packing-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-07-29-lel-packing-list/</guid><description>This is my packing list for London-Edinburgh-London 2022. I am planning to pack everything into 2 bags (seat pack and frame pack). As always I will take a sleeping bag with me that allows me to sleep wherever and whenever I want. Besides I will prepare for some British weather (although the weather forecast looks pretty good at the moment).
Clothing Bike shoes Socks (2 pairs) Cycling bibs, short (1 for cycling, 1 in my bag drop) Jersey (3, 1 for cycling and 2 in my bag drops) Armlets can&amp;rsquo;t find my leg warmers, so probably, I&amp;rsquo;ll go without Fleece jacket with hoodie Rain Jacket Rain pants Overshoes Reflective vest Helmet Buff Sun glasses (with additional transparent glasses for the night) Decided agains gloves, since I never have issues with cold hands Bags Ortlieb seat pack 11l Apidura frame pack Maybe some handlebar bag for quickly accessing my camera &amp;amp; food (undecided) Lightning Lupine Pico for the front 2 Lupine batteries 6.</description></item></channel></rss>