<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on ultra-cycling.de</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on ultra-cycling.de</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>de-de</language><copyright>© Michael Lihs 2022</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1001 Miglia Italia - My Packing List</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2024-08-03-1001-miglia-italia-packing-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2024-08-03-1001-miglia-italia-packing-list/</guid><description>This is my packing list for 1001 Miglia Italia 2024. I am planning to pack everything into 2 bags (seat pack and frame pack). As always I will take a sleeping bag with me that allows me to sleep wherever and whenever I want. Besides I will prepare for the 2 bag drops that are offered by the organizers
Clothing Bike shoes Socks (2 pairs) Cycling bibs, short (1 for cycling, 2 in my bag drops) Jersey (3, 1 for cycling and 2 in my bag drops) Armlets Leg warmers Fleece jacket with hoodie Rain Jacket Wind Jacket I will put my rain pants in the 1st bag drop, in case it turns out to be a bad decision to leave them at home Same with my overshoes Reflective vest Helmet Thin scarf to catch the sweat in my face Sun glasses (with additional transparent glasses for the night) Bags Ortlieb seat pack 16.</description></item><item><title>Bicinglés du Mont Ventoux</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2023-09-01-bicingles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 20:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2023-09-01-bicingles/</guid><description>The Challenge The Mont-Ventoux Cinglés is a permanent cycling tour that combines all 3 ascents of the famous Mont-Ventoux. The challenge is to do all three paved ascents up to the summit on the same day. Ever since I did this route in 2017 (as one of my first &amp;ldquo;long-distance challenges&amp;rdquo;), there was this idea in the back of my head to come back and do the &amp;ldquo;Bicinglés&amp;rdquo; - namely doing all three ascent twice on the same day.</description></item><item><title>London-Edinburg-London 2022 - Links, Posts &amp; Photos</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-08-26-lel-2022-links/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-08-26-lel-2022-links/</guid><description>This is a (potentially incomplete) list of articles, videos and photo streams covering the 2022 edition of London-Edinburgh-London
Did I miss anything? Please reach out and let me know if there are more links to be added!
Blog Posts Louise Bell&amp;rsquo;s blog post about being a volunteer at LEL 2022 Nick Tatt on medium.com Spanish article with video &amp;amp; plenty of great photographs Nik van Herpt&amp;rsquo;s blog post with lots of stunning b/w photos Ride report from Richard Bragg Mayank&amp;rsquo;s (C53) series of blog posts: intro day 1 day 2 day 3 day 4 day 5 day 6 John Swindells&amp;rsquo; blog post North East Randonneur on medium.</description></item><item><title>London-Edinburg-London 2022</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-08-16-lel-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-08-16-lel-2022/</guid><description>London-Edinburhg-London (or short &amp;ldquo;LEL&amp;rdquo;) is probably the second most famous brevet in Europe (after Paris-Brest-Paris). It is organised by Audax UK and takes place every 4 years. With a 1 year delay, due to the Corona pandemic, I had the great pleasure to join the 2022 edition of this iconic bike challenge. Here&amp;rsquo;s my story.
Getting there By car and ferry
After careful consideration, we decided to approach London by car.</description></item><item><title>London-Edinburg-London - my packing list</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-07-29-lel-packing-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 20:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-07-29-lel-packing-list/</guid><description>This is my packing list for London-Edinburgh-London 2022. I am planning to pack everything into 2 bags (seat pack and frame pack). As always I will take a sleeping bag with me that allows me to sleep wherever and whenever I want. Besides I will prepare for some British weather (although the weather forecast looks pretty good at the moment).
Clothing Bike shoes Socks (2 pairs) Cycling bibs, short (1 for cycling, 1 in my bag drop) Jersey (3, 1 for cycling and 2 in my bag drops) Armlets can&amp;rsquo;t find my leg warmers, so probably, I&amp;rsquo;ll go without Fleece jacket with hoodie Rain Jacket Rain pants Overshoes Reflective vest Helmet Buff Sun glasses (with additional transparent glasses for the night) Decided agains gloves, since I never have issues with cold hands Bags Ortlieb seat pack 11l Apidura frame pack Maybe some handlebar bag for quickly accessing my camera &amp;amp; food (undecided) Lightning Lupine Pico for the front 2 Lupine batteries 6.</description></item><item><title>BRM 400 Stuttgart+ Audax Suisse</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-05-20-brm-400-buch-stuttgart-buch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 20:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-05-20-brm-400-buch-stuttgart-buch/</guid><description>Prologue It was after Paris-Brest-Paris in 2019 that Thomas from Audax Suisse had the idea of letting the participants of the brevets contribute their own routes. Since it is always hard to find the secret hidden tracks and scenic highlights along the route, involing locals sounded like a great plan. Since I was still living in Stuttgart at this time, we had the idea to offer a 400km brevet from Buch (home town of Audax Suisse) to Stuttgart and back.</description></item><item><title>BRM 200 Audax Suisse</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-04-22-brm-200-bodensee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:08:48 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-04-22-brm-200-bodensee/</guid><description>The route planning Since London-Edinburgh-London is approaching at great speed (I realised there are only 3 more months for preparation), I felt the urge for some longer training distances. The idea was to get to the starting point of the BRM200 &amp;ldquo;by fair means&amp;rdquo; (by bike) and thereby add another 200km to make it a BRM 400. Besides, there is also another BRM 600 in the planning to allow for an early pre-registration for Paris-Brest-Paris in 2023.</description></item><item><title>1001 Miglia Italia 2021</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2021-11-17-1001-miglia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:08:48 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2021-11-17-1001-miglia/</guid><description>Prologue So here I was — laying on a hospital bed in some emergency room in an Italian hospital close to the city of Imola. It all happened very quickly: 15 minutes after I felt a little pain in the lower regions of my belly, I was off my bike, crumbling on the floor and calling 112 and asking for an ambulance, since I could not stand the severe pain anymore.</description></item><item><title>My journey into long distance cycling</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2021-04-09-journey-into-long-distance-cycling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 11:06:48 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2021-04-09-journey-into-long-distance-cycling/</guid><description>The first long trip I ever made on a bicycle was back when I was around 10 years old. My grandparents used to live in a town that was about 40km away from where my family used to live and we basically went there every weekend. At some point I asked my mum whether it is possible to go there by bike. One sunny day, we made it happen. It came with a surprise on how quickly got there.</description></item></channel></rss>