<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on ultra-cycling.de</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on ultra-cycling.de</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><copyright>© Michael Lihs 2022</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:08:48 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BRM 200 Audax Suisse</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-04-22-brm-200-bodensee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:08:48 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2022-04-22-brm-200-bodensee/</guid><description>The route planning Since London-Edinburgh-London is approaching at great speed (I realised there are only 3 more months for preparation), I felt the urge for some longer training distances. The idea was to get to the starting point of the BRM200 &amp;ldquo;by fair means&amp;rdquo; (by bike) and thereby add another 200km to make it a BRM 400. Besides, there is also another BRM 600 in the planning to allow for an early pre-registration for Paris-Brest-Paris in 2023.</description></item><item><title>1001 Miglia Italia 2021</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2021-11-17-1001-miglia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:08:48 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2021-11-17-1001-miglia/</guid><description>Prologue So here I was — laying on a hospital bed in some emergency room in an Italian hospital close to the city of Imola. It all happened very quickly: 15 minutes after I felt a little pain in the lower regions of my belly, I was off my bike, crumbling on the floor and calling 112 and asking for an ambulance, since I could not stand the severe pain anymore.</description></item><item><title>My journey into long distance cycling</title><link>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2021-04-09-journey-into-long-distance-cycling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 11:06:48 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://ultra-cycling.de/blog/2021-04-09-journey-into-long-distance-cycling/</guid><description>The first long trip I ever made on a bicycle was back when I was around 10 years old. My grandparents used to live in a town that was about 40km away from where my family used to live and we basically went there every weekend. At some point I asked my mum whether it is possible to go there by bike. One sunny day, we made it happen. It came with a surprise on how quickly got there.</description></item></channel></rss>